https://shop.diesel.com/en/help-show?content=terms

A NOTE ON COOKIES...
To offer you a better experience, this site uses profile cookies, even from third parties. By closing the pop-up you consent to the use of cookies. For more information or to select your preferences consult our
Cookie Policy
Accept tracking
Read More
{"orderNumber":{"valueMissing":"This field is required.","tooLong":"Please enter a valid value","tooShort":"Please enter a valid value"},"orderEmail":{"valueMissing":"The e-mail address field is required","typeMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address","patternMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address"},"contactEmail":{"valueMissing":"The e-mail address field is required","typeMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address","patternMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address"},"contactFirstName":{"valueMissing":"This field is required."},"contactSurname":{"valueMissing":"This field is required."},"contactSubject":{"valueMissing":"This field is required."},"newsletter-popup-email":{"valueMissing":"The e-mail address field is required","typeMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address","patternMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address"},"newsletter-footer-email":{"valueMissing":"The e-mail address field is required","typeMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address","patternMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address"},"newsletter-email":{"valueMissing":"The e-mail address field is required","typeMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address","patternMismatch":"Please enter a valid Email Address"}}
END OF SEASON SALE: SELECT STYLES UP TO 40% OFF!
view details
*Discount is not applicable to all merchandise; excluding, but not limited to: Special Collections, Samsonite products, Sale Products, JoggJeans and Living Collection. Cannot be combined with any other offer. Offer valid through 12/24/2020 on Diesel.com. Diesel does not provide price adjustments on prior purchases. Free shipping is applicable within the continental United States only.
SHOP NOW. PAY LATER WITH KLARNA
view details
Click here for more information.
SAME DAY DELIVERY AVAILABLE IN NYC
view details
Click here for more information.
FREE SHIPPING ON ALL ORDERS!
view details
Enjoy complimentary ground shipping on all orders. This promotion will be automatically applied at check out.
EXTENDED RETURNS
view details
*Purchases made November 11 or later are eligible for returns through January 31.
Search
Help
SUPPORT TOPICS
BACK TO HELP
FAQs
Frequently asked questions
Contact Us
Customer service details
Buy Online & Pickup In-Store
Welcome to shop.diesel.com (the "Site") which is operated for DIESEL USA Inc. ("DIESEL" or "we" or "our"). Please read our Privacy Policy carefully as it describes what and how we collect, use, share and process the personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) we collect about individuals (“Users” or “you” or “your” or "their") in connection with the services available on the Site. The Site is not intended for children and we do not collect Personal Data from children. By using the Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not want to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.
I. Our Policy
Everyone has the right to protection of their Personal Data. DIESEL respects your right to be informed regarding the collection of and other operations involving your Personal Data. We will only use data that may directly or indirectly personally identify Users when absolutely necessary. For this reason, the Site is designed in a way that our use of your Personal Data is kept to a minimum. This Privacy Policy provides you with all the information needed to understand how we collect and handle Personal Data. For further information on our Privacy Policy, please contact us at clientservice@diesel.com or at the registered office of DIESEL indicated below.
II. Personal Data We Collect
We may collect several types of Personal Data from you related to your interactions on the Site:
Personal details
E-mail address
Postal address
Social media identifiers
Credit card details
Telephone number
III. Device Information
The Site also uses technologies like Cookies, which are small text files containing random and unique alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to the hard drive of your Internet device and may identify your account or the IP address associated with the device. Cookies provide DIESEL with information related to the ways you interact with our advertising and Site, including browser type, browsing behaviors, pages and content viewed, number of new visits or log-ins, search engine referrals, affiliate referrals, which items were placed in your Shopping Cart and which were abandoned, what purchases were made and ZIP codes. Cookies are gathered directly and automatically and processed anonymously.
Typically, Cookies do not contain Personal Data, unless you previously registered on our Site or consented to disclosing Personal Data. Some Cookies allow us to optimize and tailor the Site’s services to Users’ needs and preferences, while other Cookies are necessary for using the Site and its services, including the purchase of products. If you decide to delete Cookies, especially those we believe are necessary, DIESEL cannot ensure that all web pages on the Site will be displayed or that certain services regarding finalizing online purchases will be available.
Some Cookies (known as “persistent cookies”) will remain on your computer or Internet device until you delete them, while others (known as “session cookies”) are automatically erased when you exit your Internet browser. You can set your Internet browsers to delete cookies after each session. For more details on Cookies, you should consult your Internet browser.
Please note that we do not currently respond to do-not-track signals sent by browsers. Browser settings, including do not track signals and other mechanisms, will not affect data collection and not constitute an opt-out of advertising-related cookies, personalized third-party advertising, or promotional messages from Diesel. You must use the opt-out choices described in Section IX below to opt out from such Diesel communications and third-party advertising.
IV. How We Use the Information We Collect
We may use Personal Data we collect for the following purposes:
Managing, concluding and performing transactions to purchase products on the Site;
Delivering DIESEL’S newsletter you requested and for the purposes of direct and profiled marketing communications;
If you no longer want to receive DIESEL’s newsletter or other communications, you may opt-out of such communications by the methods described in the “Opting Out” section below;
Improving your online shopping experience;
Implementing social networking features you have activated;
Communicating with you about your DIESEL account;
Enforcing the terms of use of the Site or otherwise manage our business.
V. How We Share Your Information
We may share your Personal Data with our third-party service providers for purposes discussed above. Any disclosures or transfer of your Personal Data to third-party service providers will be in accordance with US law. All third-party service providers are obligated to maintain the security and confidentiality of your Personal Data, and to only process your Personal Data in accordance with our instructions and Privacy Policy. By having an opportunity to review this Privacy Policy prior to providing any Personal Data, you consent to third-party service providers receiving and processing your Personal Data as discussed above. If you would not like us to share such Personal Data with third-parties, please refer to the “Refusal to Disclose Personal Data” section below. You may obtain an up-to-date list of third-party service providers by sending an email to: clientservice@diesel.com.
Our third-party service providers may also have access to the Personal Data of people who are not Users of the Site based on information that you directly disclosed on the Site, in the following instances:
A User who purchases a product on the Site to be mailed to a friend;
A User who pays for a product on the Site who is different from the recipient of the product; or
A User who recommends a product on sale on the Site to a friend.
In all of the above cases, you must make sure you receive the consent from third-parties prior to disclosing their Personal Data and inform them about DIESEL’s Privacy Policy. DIESEL will treat this Personal Data in accordance with its Privacy Policy, just as it does your Personal Data. However, you will be liable in connection with the disclosure of third-parties’ Personal Data, if you failed to obtain the third-parties express consent to disclose their Personal Data or for any improper or unlawful use of that data.
Lastly, DIESEL may share your information with third-parties, unrelated to the services provided on the Site, when we believe it is necessary or appropriate: (a) as required or necessary in order to comply with applicable law (including laws outside your country of residence); (b) to protect itself against liability; (c) to respond to subpoenas, judicial processes, or legitimate requests by law enforcement officials; (d) to purchasers in connection with any sale, assignment, or other transfer of all or a part of our business or company; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property; (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages we may sustain.
VI. Refusal to Disclose Personal Data
Providing Personal Data to DIESEL or our third-party service providers is always optional. However, some of your Personal Data, particularly your personal details, email address, postal address, credit/debit card numbers and telephone number, are necessary for pursuing the commercial purposes of the Site. Your refusal to provide DIESEL with the Personal Data needed for performing the above purposes could prevent DIESEL from processing your order of products on the Site or from fulfilling obligations required by law and other regulations. Personal Data other than that required for processing orders or fulfilling legal or contractual obligations is optional and will not have any affect on the purchase of products on the Site.
We will periodically inform you whether disclosing your Personal Data to DIESEL or its third-party service providers is necessary as indicated by the (*) symbol or optional, as well as any consequences for not disclosing such data.
VII. Security
We have adopted commercially reasonable security measures to protect your Personal Data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, or unauthorized disclosure or access and we encrypt credit card numbers from e-commerce transactions conducted on our Site using secure socket layer (SSL) technology. However, no method of internet transmission or electronic storage is 100% secure or error free. If you have any reason to believe that your interactions with the Site are no longer secure, please notify us immediately at the address provided below.
VIII. How Users Can Access or Change Their Personal Data
If you wish to update your Personal Data to ensure it is correct, up-to-date and complete or exercise any right of access, rectification, deletion, or opposition to the processing of your Personal Data that you may have under applicable law, please contact us at clientservice@diesel.com.
In order to protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your Personal Data. Any request to access your Personal Data will be answered within a reasonable timeframe and in no event shall it exceed 30 days.
IX. Opting Out of Diesel Communications and Third-Party Advertising
If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from DIESEL, you may opt out of receiving such emails by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email newsletter you receive from us, or, if you created an online account when you registered to receive our emails, you may log into your account and make changes to your communication preferences. If you are having difficulty unsubscribing from our marketing emails using the above methods, please contact us directly at the email or mailing addresses listed below under “Contacting Us.”
Please allow ample time for us to process your request. However, please note that even if you opt out from receiving marketing communications, we may need to send you service-related communications and may need to keep information we have collected about you for record-keeping, research and other purposes.
You can also generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.
X. Links to Other Websites
From time to time, DIESEL may include links on the Site to third party websites. Please pay attention when you connect to these websites and read their terms and conditions of use and privacy policies carefully. DIESEL does not control or monitor such websites or their web content. The Privacy Policy of the Site does not apply to any third party websites and DIESEL will not be liable for the content, privacy policies or processing of your Personal Data while you are visiting any third-party websites.
XI. User’s California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, you may have the right to request and receive certain information about a company’s disclosure of your personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing use, and your choices with respect to such disclosures. Because we do not share your personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing use unless you are first given the opportunity to opt in or out, we are exempt from this requirement. If you still wish to learn more about our compliance with this requirement, please contact us at the address listed below.
XII. Contacting Us
Please direct any inquiries related to this Privacy Policy or Personal Data we have collected about you by mail to DIESEL USA Inc., 220 W. 19th St., New York, New York USA 10011 or by email at clientservice@diesel.com.
XIII. Changes to DIESEL’S Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to amend all or part of this Privacy Policy from time to time. The version published on the Site is the version currently in force. Changes to this Privacy Policy are communicated by placing a notice on the Site stating “Revised Privacy Policy.” Changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately once published in a revised Privacy Policy posted on this page unless otherwise noted. Your use of the Site following any amendments, indicates your consent to the practices described in the revised Privacy Policy. DIESEL invites Users to periodically review the Privacy Policy to be informed of any relevant changes, especially before providing any data to DIESEL.
NEED HELP?
If you have any question or need help with your account, you may contact us to assist you.
We will respond to every message within 1 working day. Monday to Saturday, excluding national holidays.
CLIENT SERVICE
Phone: 855-482-1155
Monday - Friday: 9am - 9pm EST
Saturday: 10am - 9pm EST, excluding national holidays.
